Previously on...
前情提要
Bree's husband felt rejected.
布里的丈夫有了挫败感
I think it's strange to see my wife billed
看到自己的太太以"范德坎普夫人"的称号公著于世
As "mrs. van de kamp."
-我觉得很不舒服
it's how I'm known.
我是以此而出名的
Is there a mr. van de kamp?
谈谈范德坎普先生吧
no, uh, mr. van de kamp is deceased.
很抱歉  范德坎普先生已经过世了
Would it have killed you to have mentioned me?
要你提一下我  就这么难吗
It's because I went to jail, isn't it?
因为我进过监狱  是吗
lynette's husband was excited.
勒奈特的丈夫非常兴奋
We're gonna start a garage band!
我们要成立一个车库乐队啦
I thought you were the one who said
你不是曾说过
you wanted to spend more time with your family
要把更多的时间放在家庭吗
guys need to blow off steam.
男人们需要释放一下激情
Edie's new husband had a past
伊迪的新丈夫有一段往事
you've been here six weeks,
你来这里已经6周了
And you don't seem any closer
我没发现
to coming to terms with your rage
你的易怒情绪有所缓解
I've come to terms with it,
我的情绪问题早已解决
And I like it just the way it is
现在感觉很良好
which remained a mystery.
往事充满着悬疑
I just think it's odd that you're married to some guy.
我觉得跟一个你完全不了解的男人结婚
You don't know anything about him.
是件很奇怪的事情
She kept asking me all this stuff about your background
她不停地询问我关于你的背景
And susan tried to move on.
苏珊开始新的生活
-I sort of started seeing someone.
-我开始与人约会了
good for you.
不错啊
Every year, ms. elenora butters
爱伦诺拉.巴特老师每年
would ask her kindergarten class
都会要求幼儿园的孩子们
to draw a picture of their families
画一张全家福
which she would then display on "meet the teacher" night.
然后在家长会上把画展示出来
That's how ty richmond's parents
因此瑞奇曼的父母在画作上
saw his depiction of their fighting...
看到他们吵架的情景
And amy hines' parents
而爱米.海因斯的父母
saw her portrayal of their drinking.
则看到了他们酗酒的样貌
And jason monte's parents
杰森.蒙特的父母
saw his illustration of their hygiene.
见到了家里脏乱的情形
You see, ms. butters felt it was important for parents
很显然  巴特老师认为通过孩子的视角
for parents to see themselves through their children's eyes.
让家长了解其自己  是相当重要的
She knew the experience...
她见怪不怪了
Ed, he's got me vacuuming in my bra.
艾德  画里我只戴着胸罩在吸尘
Do I do that?
我有这么做过吗
Could be very educational.
这相当有教育意义
I know, I know.
我知道  对不起
Did I not say 7:00? you missed their little show.
我难道没说是7点吗  你错过了精彩的表演
M.j. was tooth decay.
M.j.很不高兴
crosstown traffic killed me.
镇上大塞车
And I told you to videotape it.
我告诉你把它录下来
did you tell me to take off the lens cap?
但你没告诉我要把镜头盖取下
Next time, be more specific.
拜托下次教详细点
Mr. delfino, glad you made it.
德尔非诺先生  很高兴你来了
Uh, did you get to see m.j.'s artwork?
你看了m.j.的画作了吗
No, not yet. can't wait.
还没呢  都等不及了
Oh, hey, look at that. There we are
哦  你看啊这里  这就是我们
standing in front of the house.
站在我们家门前
Look what he did with my hair.
他把我头发画成什么了
I kind of like the bangs.
有所改变也不错
yeah, look, he put a wrench in my pocket.
你瞧  我口袋里还有一个扳手
And see how big my muscles are?
看看我肌肉多丰满
which's a good thing cause a shark attacking the house
对啊  因为有个小偷正想闯入
Hey, daddy.
爸爸
Hey, buddy. your mommy and i
儿子  我和你妈妈
Were just looking at your wonderful painting.
正在欣赏你优秀的作品
You like it?
你喜欢吗
I love it, especially how big and strong you made me look.
很喜欢  尤其把我画得这么壮实
That's not you. that's jackson.
那不是你  那是杰克逊
See the paintbrush in his pocket?
看到口袋里的油漆刷了吗
Oh, who's jackson?
谁是杰克逊
He paints our house...
在我妈妈把他灌醉
Until my mom makes him drink wine and have a sleepover.
并和他上床之前  他是我们家的油漆工
Because...
因为...
Mike and I are divorced, so that's why...
我和麦克离婚了  因此...
It was supposed to be a picture of the family,
按理这应该是一张全家福的
So you should've put your daddy in it.
你应当把你爸爸画进去
I did.
我画了
Oh, the... the bug with the little hat?
哦  是那个...戴着帽子的小人吗
That's you,
那就是你
'cause you're always so far away.
因为你总是不在家
Oh, yeah, that's, um...
是的  看来...
Now I see me.
我终于找到我了
Yes... every year,
是的...每一年
Ms. elenora butters would ask her class
爱伦诺拉.巴特老师每年仍要求学生们
To draw a picture of their families,
画一张全家福
Even though she knew the portraits...
她知道肖像中的人物
Might not be that flattering.
是现实生活的真实写照
If you look closely into the faces of your friends,
如果你仔细观察一下你朋友的面容
You'll see it.
你会看到
-Hey!
-嗨
hi!
嗨
-Congratulations!
-恭喜你啊
hi!
大家好
Come on in!
进来吧
Right behind their smiles,
在她们的笑容背后
You will see a certain green-eyed monster,
隐藏着充满嫉妒的神情
And then you'll understand
然后你会明白
How envious they are of your well-kept home...
对于你的持家有道  她们有多么忌妒
Your delicious recipes...
你那美味的菜式
And your tasteful possessions.
和令人垂涎的财富
Here's my cookbook.
这是我的烹饪书
But you'll have to work hard to see the jealousy,
但你必须仔细观察  才能察觉嫉妒
Because good friends always work hard to hide it
因为好朋友总是努力把嫉妒心隐藏起来
Look at you, right on the cover!
你看呀  简直就是封面女郎
These are advanced copies.
这几本是精装版
I wanted you to be the first to have them.
我要让你们成为第一批读者
Oh, and look, you signed it-- "to lynette,
哦  看哪  你还签上了"致勒奈特
The sweetest, most wonderful friend I've ever known."
我最可爱  最亲密的伙伴"
"to susan, the sweetest, most--"
"致苏珊  我最可爱  最..."
We don't have to read them out loud.
我们不用念得这么响
Don't mind me, ladies.
别介意  女士们
I'm just grabbing a kiss on my way to the salt mines.
我要去岩盐坑上班了  来个告别之吻
You have a good day.
祝你工作愉快
Thanks, babe. oh, did you show them the ad?
谢谢  宝贝  你把广告给她们看了吗
yeah. oh, I almost forgot.
我差点忘了
Isn't this nice?
是不是很棒
They're running it next month in "woman's day."
他们要在下月的刊登
You're gonna be in magazines, too?
你会出现在杂志上吗
They've come up with this whole marketing plan
他们已经拿出了整套市场开拓计划
Radio, print, book signings.
广播  出版  签名售书
-Wow! isn't it fantastic?
-那真是太美妙了
no, it's horrible!
不  这一点都不好玩
She's gonna become this famous author
她将成为著名的作家
And have no time at all for us.
没空陪我们了
No, come on, gaby. you know that bree will never change.
不会的  加布  布里永远是布里
Thank you, katherine.
谢谢  凯瑟琳
I will never become stuck-up and full of myself.
我绝对不会高傲自满的
I didn't say that. I said you'd never change.
我没那么说  我是指你不会改变的
Very funny.
真有意思
I don't think you've to worry about me becoming famous
我觉得你们不用担心我出名的事情
You have a marketing plan.
你都有市场计划了
You wanna see my marketing plan?
想要看看我的卖场计划吗
"milk, bread, vodka, condoms--"
"牛奶  面包  伏特加  避孕套"
-Could I see that? I'd love to read it.
-我能看看吗  很想看一下
why?
为什么
Well, back before I consecrated my life to mozzarella,
我当年做意大利干酪的销售
Marketing was sort of what I did.
也有整套的市场推广计划
Oh, right! of course.
哦  当然
I would, uh, love to hear your thoughts.
我很乐意听取你的意见
So you're still gonna
那么即使你名声远扬
Wanna hang out with us, even when you're totally fabulous,
依然还会和我们一起聚会的吧
And we're still nobodies?
我们还是自己人吧
Girls, you are making way too much of this.
女生们  你们说过头了
I am not a bit more fabulous than any one of you.
我不见得比你们厉害多少
Excuse me.
稍等
What is it, andrew?
怎么了  安德鲁
I hope you're free for lunch on the 12th,
我希望你12号午餐时间暂无安排
'cause the chamber of commerce
因为商委会刚提名你
Just named you businesswoman of the year.
为今年的"年度商业女性"
Oh, my god! that is so amazing!
哦  我的天哪  真是太棒了
The, uh, dry cleaner just, found my sweater
干洗店终于找到我的毛衣了
Hi.
喂
Orson, I have amazing news.
我有个惊人的消息
-The chamber of commerce just called.
-商委会刚刚打电话来了
oh? what about?
哦  说什么了
I wanna buy you lunch and tell you in person.
我和你一起吃午饭  我们面谈
I will be at your office in two minutes.
我2分钟内就到你办公室
Uh, no! no, don't come to my office.
别  别  别来我办公室
You know, I can't have lunch now. um, I'm in a meeting.
我现在不能吃午饭  我在开会
Well, I'll wait in reception until it's over.
那我到前台等你好了
No, it'll take hours.
不  可能要好几个小时
It's a very urgent, high-level stuff.
是个紧急会议  事关重要
What kind of meeting is it?
到底是什么会啊
George, hey!
乔治  搞什么啊
Turn that radio down!
把收音机调小一点
-Where are you?
-你在哪啊
I told you, I'm in a meeting.
不是告诉你了  我在开会
I gotta go.
我要挂了
I'll see you soon.
我尽快来见你
Yes, you will.
是的  的确很快
Mike! what's going on?
麦克  怎么了
Daddy got me a bike.
爸爸给我买了辆自行车
Yes, I see. and here,
是的  我看到了  就在这里
Mommy thought we'd agreed to wait till your birthday.
我们不是说好了  到过生日才买吗
can you teach me to ride it?
你能教我怎样骑吗
No, not today. I gotta go install a water heater.
今天不行  我要去修理热水器
But, uh, you keep practicing,
不过  你可以先练练
And the next afternoon I have free,
明天下午我有空
we'll bust off those training wheels
我们一起学骑车
and go kick up some dirt. okay?
轮子飞转  尘土飘扬  如何
okay
好吧
All right.
去吧
Oh, my god.
哦  我的天哪
This is about m.j.'s drawing, isn't it?
这都是因为m.j.的画  是不是
What?
什么
He does not love jackson more than you.
比起杰克逊  他肯定更爱你
He knows who his father is.
他知道谁才是他父亲
I know that. Can't a guy get his kid a bike
这我知道  难道给自己孩子买辆小车
without being psychoanalyzed?
就代表心存嫉妒吗
So you're totally fine with that drawing?
那对于那幅画  你没事了吧
Well, I won't go sticking it on my fridge anytime soon,
虽然我不会高调地把它贴到冰箱上去
But yeah.
但我没事
Look, I'm glad you're dating a nice guy.
我很高兴你能和一个好男人约会
I'm glad he likes my kid, and my kid likes him.
孩子与他彼此能合得来  这点我也很高兴
Here's a bike. that's all it is.
这只是一辆自行车而已  别无他意
Hey, guys.
你们好啊
Jackson, look at my new bike!
杰克逊  看看我的新车
Pretty cool.
真酷啊
Uh, that's a custom titanium frame.
这是由钛合金定做的
Make sure m.j. knows that.
让m.j.了解一下
Mommy, can bethany go home now?
妈妈  贝瑟妮可以回家了吗
Honey, she's only been here 20 minutes.
宝贝  她才来玩了20分钟而已
We invited her over to play, so go play.
我们本来就是邀请她来玩的  好好玩去
But all she does is spin.
但她只会玩转圈
Honey, we want bethany to be our friend,
宝贝  我们要让贝瑟妮成为我们的朋友
So if she wants to spin, just suck it up and spin.
要是她喜欢转圈  那就跟她学学一起转
Why are you show that little weirdo down juanita's throat?
你干嘛非要让胡安妮塔跟这个小怪人一起玩
That little weirdo is the key to you and I having more sex.
这个小怪人是能否让你我做爱的关键所在
I know I should ask a few questions, but I'm in.
这点我喜欢  但到底是为什么
Bethany's mom hosts a weekly playdate.
贝瑟妮的妈妈每周都会举行小朋友聚会
I'm trying to get juanita an invitation.
我要试着让胡安妮塔也获得邀请
How does that lead to quality time with your boobs?
这和我跟你做爱又有什么关系
Carlos, the only time you and I have to ourselves
卡洛斯  我和你只有晚间有时间
Is late at night, but by that time, we're too exhausted.
但那时候  你我都精疲力竭了
And now that we have celia in afternoon preschool,
现在每天下午都有未上学的西利娅要照顾
All we have to do is unload juanita,
所以我们必须这样做才能摆脱胡安妮塔
And then we can get back to doing the nasty.
这样才能回来好好做爱
This doesn't seem right.
这样会不会不太好
I mean, dumping our kid off on some unsuspecting woman
把我们自己的孩子扔给别的女人
So that we can have sex?
这样我们才能做爱
Wake up! playdates were invented by mothers
你醒醒吧  妈妈们发明儿童聚会
For this exact purpose.
目的就是为了这个
Shopping, sex, drinking in the afternoon--
购物  做爱  在下午喝酒
Playdates make all these things possible.
只有儿童聚会才能实现这些
I-i don't know.
我...不知道
I feel bad making my kid play with someone
强迫我们孩子跟她不喜欢的人一起玩
That she obviously doesn't like.
让我觉得很糟糕
Bethany's mom'll take juanita once a week 2 whole hours
贝瑟妮的妈妈可以每周把胡安妮塔带走2个小时
That is sex and a nap.
正好可以做爱加小睡
Juanita!
胡安妮塔
I don't hear you spinning!
我听不到你转圈的声音
I don't understand. you said the job was going so well.
我不明白  你说过你的工作一帆风顺
It was. then three weeks ago,
本来是很顺利  三周前
My parole officer left me a message at work.
我的假释官在我工作时留了个口信
That's when they found out I lied on my application
就在那时他们发现我申请工作时撒了谎
When I said I didn't have a criminal record.
我申请时说我没有案底
So you've been pretending to go to work for three weeks?
所以你这三周都在假装工作
I know you're angry.
我知道你怒火中烧
Honey...I'm not angry
亲爱的   我没有动怒
I'm hurt that you didn't feel like you could tell me.
你不想把这些告诉我  我很难受
I was embarrassed.
我感觉很困窘
Bree, when we married, I was the breadwinner.
布里  我们结婚时  是我养家糊口
Now you--you have your company and you have your book.
现在你开了自己的公司  也出了书
I-i'm a felon who can't hold on to a job.
我是个连饭碗也保不住的重罪犯
Orson, we're partners. we share everything.
奥森  我们是伙伴  我们共有一切
Any success I have
我所取得的任何成就
Is just as much yours as it is mine.
和你的分量相同
Thank you, darling.
谢谢你  亲爱的
So...
那么
Why did the chamber of commerce call?
商会打电话来干什么
Apparently, we've been named businesswoman of the year.
很明显  我们被提名为今年的商界女强人
Is that good enough?!
是不是很棒
Wow! you'd be killer in our band.
你会成为我们乐队的杀手锏
I mean, wouldn't he be killer, dave?
他肯定会成为杀手锏  不是吗  大卫
Uh, donald, why don't you let us talk it over,
唐纳德  何不让我们商量一下呢
And we'll get back to you?
-我们回头会找你
no problem.
没问题
I have to get back to the office anyway.
反正我要去上班
Quarterly tax time has got me swamped.
每季度一到交税  我就忙得不可开交
Well, we'll--we'll definitely call you today.
我们今天肯定会给你打电话
Thanks, gentlemen.
谢谢  先生们
Don't you think he crushed it?
你不觉得他棒极了吗
He was good... you know, technically.
技术上讲  他表现得不错
-He didn't really have heart.
-他没有用心投入
what do you mean?
什么意思
When he play voodoo child, it was like hendrix has risen
他演奏巫毒小子时  就像是亨德里克斯附身
what about mike? I thought that's who we were gonna get
迈克怎么样  他才是我们要找的人
Well, I asked, but he said he's too busy.
我问过他  但他说他最近很忙
Too busy to live a little? not gonna fly.
忙得不会生活了吗  这可不是借口
Call him. give him my number. I'll talk to him.
-打电话给他  把我号码给他  我来说
okay, sure.
好吧  当然
But--but what about donald?
可唐纳德怎么样
I mean, 'cause if we don't get mike, I wanna make s--
我是说  要是迈克来不了  我想确保
Tom, donald's out, all right?
汤姆  唐纳德出局了  好吗
Have mike call me.
让麦克给我打电话
What a rehearsal.
好一场排练啊
Dave and I were smokin'.
大卫和我都冒烟了
Did you hear us?
你听到我们的声音了吗
Lynette?
勒奈特
Lynette.
I'm sorry. what?
很抱歉  你说什么
Never mind.
没事了
What are you working on? what, is this bree's ad stuff?
你在干嘛  这是布里的广告吗
Oh, god, no. her agency really whiffed... hmm?
不  帮她办事的人实在太逊了
So I'm coming up with a whole new campaign.
所以我在策划一个新的推广计划
I was looking through my old portfolio
我在查一些我以前的资料
For inspiration. mm-hmm.
找点灵感
Oh! I remember this one.
我记得这个
"feet? meet your new best friends." it was a classic.
脚  见见你最好的新朋友吧  真是经典啊
You know, it's been years since I looked through this stuff.
我已经好几年没有翻阅这些东西了
I'd forgotten I was... kinda great.
我都忘了我曾如此辉煌
You were awesome!
你当时棒极了
I mean, come on. how lucky is bree
拜托  布里多幸运啊
have a neighbor that used to be a big advertising hotshot
能有个前广告巨头当邻居
Well, maybe I'm the lucky one.
或许我才是那个幸运儿
This could be a perfect way for me
可能这是个绝好的机会
To stick my toe back in the business.
让我能重操旧业
Nothing big, maybe just pick up some freelance work.
没什么大不了  可能只从事些自由职业的工作
honey, if you do that, where you gonna find the time
亲爱的  你要这样  哪有时间
-For the family and the restaurant?
-照顾家庭和餐馆呢
well, gee, I don't know.
天  我不知道
I guess the same place that you find time for your ga band
你不也有时间组建车库乐队吗
Lynette, I'm just saying that if--if you...
勒奈特  我只是说你要是
Okay, I dropped off celia at preschool,
好啦  我把西利娅送去幼儿园了
And juanita's at her playdate.
胡安妮塔在她玩伴家里
Drop trou.
脱裤子
Why don't you put on that sexy red teddy?
你何不穿上那条性感的红色连衣裤呢
Can I ask why? I mean, you can't see it.
我能问为什么吗  你根本看不见
Yeah, but I can feel it,
是啊  可我感觉得到
And I love the sensation of sliding silk off your body.
我喜欢丝绸从你身上滑落下来的感觉
What's it like, carlos?
感觉怎么样  卡洛斯
What?
什么
Sex as a blind man.
作为一个盲人的性爱
I mean, you used to be so visual.
我是说  你以前能看得见
Is it still as good?
感觉还像以前那么好吗
Oh, it's better.
更胜一筹
I mean, having to rely on
我是说  不得不依靠
Your senses of touch and taste and smell...
你的触觉  味觉  和嗅觉
It's actually way more intense.
实际上更激情四射
Really? you're so lucky.
真的吗  你真幸运
What, you want blind sex?
什么  你想体会盲人性爱吗
I think I can arrange that.
我可以给你安排啊
Hey there.
你在啊
Looks like somebody's job interview went well.
看起来某人的面试很成功啊
Nope. they turned me down flat.
错啦  他们直截了当拒绝了我
Aw. but as I was driving home, it suddenly hit me.
但我开车回家时  突然灵机一动
I may be persona non grata at every company in this town,
可能这镇上的每家公司都不欢迎我
But there's at least one employer I know
但至少有一个雇主
Who would love to hire me.
愿意雇用我
Oh. who?
谁啊
You.
你
You wanna work here?
你想在这里工作吗
Why not?
为什么不
I'm great with food. I understand business.
我对食物很在行  了解商业运作方式
I can't beat the commute.
而且也不计较酬劳
Well, that's certainly an intriguing notion.
这个想法看似很有意思
But wouldn't it be awkward having me as your boss?
但我做你的上司不是很尴尬吗
Absolutely.
当然
But as you said in the park,
但你在公园也说了
We share everything.
我们共享一切
So I would be more of a... partner.
所以我不仅仅是个搭档
Partners? oh.
搭档
bree, would you give me a hand with this arrangement?
布里  你过来帮忙一下好吗
Just give me a sec.
等我一会儿
I think the lilies need their own vase.
百合花需要用自己的花瓶装
If you hire him, I will cut you with these scissors
如果你雇他  我会把你剪成破布的
I don't think we need to do that.
我们不需要这么做
I think they're crowding the irises out.
他们要把鸢尾花挤出去
Just like he's trying to crowd me out.
就像他在把我排挤出去一样
You already have a partner, remember?
你已经有个搭档了  记得吗
Oh, well, I think the irises and the lilies
鸢尾花和百合花
Could work together.
-可以一起工作
nope. one of them has to go.
不  必须放弃一个
-If I may offer an opinion
-如果我能给点意见
not a good time, orson.
现在不是时候  奥森
Tell him now,
马上告诉他
Or I will walk.
要不我走
Orson, you really don't wanna work with me.
奥森  你实在不会想和我共事
I mean, you only see me at home.
你只看得见我在家的样子
But work, when the pressure on, I can be a bit of a handful.
但是工作时  我在压力下难以控制自己情绪
-Katherine see how I get.
-凯瑟琳知道我的德行
yes. bitchy, tyrannical, shrill
泼辣  暴躁  恼人
He gets it, dear.
够了  亲爱的
Honey, you're my partner in life.
亲爱的  你是我一生的伙伴
But if we want to keep it that way,
但我们要保持美满的婚姻
We shouldn't mix marriage and business.
我们不该混淆婚姻和事业
But no one else will hire me.
但没人肯聘用我
Well, you've only been looking for a few weeks.
你找工作才花了几周时间而已
I mean, give it another... say, month or two,
再花些时间  比方说  一两个月
And if you still haven't found anything,
如果你还一无所获
Then we'll revisit the idea. okay?
我们一定会从新考虑  好吗
Okay.
好吧
It was just a thought.
我只是想想而已
Oh, so what'd you think?
你觉得怎样
Oh, my god, you were right.
我的天  你说的没错
Blind sex is incredible.
盲人性爱太不可思议了
Ahh, give me ten more minutes and an energy bar,
再给我十分钟和一个能量条
And we can go one more time.
我们还能再干一场
No, I think we're done.
不  到此为止
Honey!
亲爱的
What are you doing home? I thought you were at bethany's.
你在家里干什么  我以为你在贝瑟妮家呢
I got a tummyache. her mom brought me back.
我胃疼  她妈妈就把我送回来了
Well, how long have you been standing there?
你站在那里多久了
I don't know. what were you two doing?
不知道  你们俩刚才在干嘛
Um, we were, uh...
我们在
We were wrestling. wrestling.
我们在扭打  扭打
Did daddy hurt you? you were making loud noises.
爸爸弄疼你了吗  你刚才叫得好大声
No! no, that wasn't real.
不  不  那不是真的
Sometimes I fake it when I wrestle with daddy.
有时我和你爸爸扭打的时候就这么装
Please don't wrestle with mommy.
请别和妈妈扭打
You're too big. you could hurt her.
你块头太大了  会弄疼她
Yeah, carlos, stop that.
是的  卡洛斯  别再那样了
Okay, go to your room,
好的  回你房间去
And I'm gonna bring you something for your tummy.
我去给你拿点胃药
I think she bought it.
她应该当真了
You mean the story of how daddy beats up mommy?
你是说爸爸毒打妈妈的谎话吗
Relax. I told her I was fine.
别紧张  我说了我没事
look, I could hear the worry in her voice.
我听得出她很担心
Why don't we just tell her the truth?
我们为什么不干脆告诉她真相
What, that sometimes mommy rides daddy
什么  有时妈妈骑在爸爸身上
Like a mechanical bull to get jewelry?
就像骑着机器牛去抢珠宝吗
She's 5. she's too young to understand either half of that.
她才5岁  根本不可能明白
It's the facts of life.
这是性的基本知识
She's gonna learn 'em eventually,
她终究会了解
And it's the most natural thing in the world.
这是世上最自然而然的事
Carlos, if she was standing there any longer than 5 minutes
卡洛斯  要是她刚才多站5分钟
There was nothing natural about what she saw.
她看到的就不仅仅是自然了
By the way, thank you for that.
此外  谢谢你那样
Hello?
喂
Hey, it's me. listen,
是我  听着
I've got some free time,
我正好有时间
So I thought I'd come over
我想过去
And teach m.j. how to ride his new bike.
教M.J.骑他的新车
great. he's so excited to learn.
太棒了  他迫不及待呢
Are you sure he's ready to go without training wheels?
你确定他不需要护轮就能骑了吗
Oh, he'll probably have to take a few spills,
他可能还得要摔上几跤呢
But luckily, he'll have his old man there to pick him up.
幸运的是  他有老爸扶他起来
Yeah. he's been asking when you're coming.
是的  他一直在问你什么时候来
I can't wait to tell him. I know he'll be just...
我等不及要告诉他  我知道他会...
All right!
好吧
What's the matter?
怎么了
Spider. big one. gotta go!
蜘蛛  好大一只  我得走了
Mommy, look, no training wheels.
妈妈  看  没有用护轮
I know! you did great!
我知道  做得好
Jackson, can I see you a sec?
杰克逊  借一步说话
That was amazing! he learned so fast.
真是不可思议  他学车突飞猛进
you know what I learned? mike is on his way over here
这我看出来了  但问题是迈克正赶过来
To teach his son how to ride the bike he bought--
教他儿子怎样骑他买的车
Something he was looking forward to until you ruined it.
他期盼已久的事被你毁于一旦
W-why didn't you tell me that?
你为什么没告诉我
I didn't know I had to tell you
我怎么知道我还有义务告诉你
not to steal a father's precious moment.
别抢走一个爸爸的宝贵时光
M.j.--he just kept asking me. he--he made me do it.
M.J.  他不停地求我  一定要我教他
You could've walked away.
你可以置之不理啊
No, I couldn't!
不  我不能
He said, "please!"
他说  "求你了"
Damn it.
该死
As you can see, the graphic works just as well
很明显  这幅图画好象
On a free-standing display unit. neat, huh?
在一个独立的版面上  很优雅
Goodness, lynette.
天呐  勒奈特
When you offered to share your thoughts on my campaign,
当时你提出要对我的推广活动出点主意
I wasn't expecting anything quite so... elaborate.
我没有想到会制作得如此...精美
Well, who knew your marketing guys were such lame-os?
谁知道你的推销员都那么差劲
What they came up with is so...tepid
他们的想法都太...无趣了
Um, I think "understated" was what they were going for.
我想他们是在追求"朴素"
Well, they overshot and wound up in "bland,"
但朴素过头  就会造成"乏味"
Right on the border of "sucky."
近乎濒临"烂"
You need to grab your audience, just grab 'em.
你要抓住你的受众  要夺人眼球
I've gone for jazzier colors,
我使用的颜色相当"奔放"
Bolder fonts.
你看这加粗的字
Oh, I have really played up the whole nostalgia angle.
我的宣传卖点就是"怀旧"
"let mrs. van de kamp
让范德坎普太太
Turn your oven into a time machine."
带你进入时间机器
I see women really responding to that.
我想只要是女性肯定会赞同
Do you?
能么
Because I see children
可我看到孩子们
Crawling into ovens, hoping to see dinosaurs.
爬到炉子里  希望能看到恐龙
I've got a whole bunch of alternatives.
我预备了很多备用方案
Oh, lynette, I appreciate everything you've done.
勒奈特  你做的每件事我都很欣赏
But I've actually approved the old campaign,
但我必须要让这次活动被公众认可
And I can't just tell them I've changed my mind.
我不能告诉他们我改主意了
You don't have to. I'll be the bad guy.
你没必要  我才是那个坏事的人
Just tell 'em you've hired me,
告诉他们你雇了我
And I'll go in there, six-guns ablazing.
我会去那  跟他们理论
So... do we have a deal?
那么  咱们达成一致了么
Just give me the word.
说一声就行
No.
没有
No?
Sorry, but I prefer their campaign.
对不起  我更喜欢他们构思的计划
But mine is better.
但是我的更好
Well, you're... entitled to think so, but I don't.
你的... 貌似还不错  但我觉得不行
Look, bree...
布里...
I think I know a little more about marketing than you do.
我认为我在营销上比你略胜一筹
When I was in it, I owned this town.
我刚进这行的时候  整个镇都惟我所属
I had every big account.
各大帐目都是我管理的
Hell, I was even named businesswoman of the year.
我甚至是"年度商业女性"
Oh. well, I'm familiar with that award.
我很熟悉那个奖
In fact, I'm this year's recipient.
事实上  我是今年的获奖者
Really?
-真的
yes.
是的
There's a luncheon on the 12th. I do hope you can make it.
12号有一个午宴  你一定要过来
By the way,
顺便说一下
You're right about those colors.
你选的那些颜色很棒
Very... jazzy.
非常..."奔放"
Come on, m.j. your daddy's waiting.
来吧  m.j.  你爸爸等你呢
Mommy, I don't wanna fall.
妈妈  我不想摔倒
Oh, honey.
宝贝儿
You know how you like to push the button
你记得每次坐电梯
When we go on the elevator,
你总爱玩按钮吗
And if somebody else pushes it first, it makes you sad?
如果有人先按下  你就会难过
But I don't wanna fall.
但是  我不想摔倒
Just listen. daddy really wanted to be the one
听着  爸爸特别想
To teach you to ride your bike, and if you can already do it,
亲自教你骑车  如果你会骑了
It's gonna make him sad.
这才会让他难过呢
So just let daddy push the button. understand?
就让爸爸去按那个按钮吧  明白么
Wow, he's really picking it up fast.
他骑的真快啊
Yeah. I think it's just beginner's luck. uh-huh.
我想是初学者有好运
Are you sure he hasn't been practicing?
-你确定他没练习过么
no.
没
He was absolutely waiting for you.
他真的是在等你
You know, I think I'm gonna go check his helmet.
我得去检查下他的头盔
What are you doing? we talked about this.
你在干什么  我们说好的
-You're supposed to be new.
-你本该像个新手的
I don't want to fall. I'm scared
我不想摔倒  我害怕
Oh! of what? you're 3 inches off the ground.
怕什么  你离地才3英寸
You're completely padded. so just do what I say
而且全身都是护垫  就照我说的做
Wobble, wobble. "daddy, look at me!" crash.
先假装摇晃  ""爸爸  看我"  然后摔倒
He was just telling me how glad he is to have his dad here
他刚跟我说  爸爸在这看他真开心
really? 'cause I almost feel like he doesn't even need me
真的么  我觉得他根本不需要我
oh, that's just silly.
你别犯傻
Whoops-a-daisy! oh, it's a good thing your dad's here
哎呦  怎么啦  幸好你爸爸在这
To teach you how to do it right.
教你怎么骑
oh, looking good, buddy, but remember,
看着还不错  但是记住
When you stop, you gotta put your foot down first.
当你要停的时候  先把脚放下来
-Oh, what, does that hurt right there, buddy?
-是伤在这里了吗
oh, he's fine
他没事
No, mommy. it hurts.
不  妈妈  我伤着了
-This is all my fault.
-这都是我的错
oh, will you stop?
你别这么说了
The doctor said it was just a sprain.
医生说只是扭伤
I know, but still, I shouldn't have pushed it.
我知道  我不该让他自己骑的
You know, why look for blame? kids fall.
为什么要自责呢  小孩经常摔交
If you have to find fault, Blame the pavement, not yourself...
非要怪罪  就怪人行道好了  别怪你自己
Or me.
或者是我
Mommy!
妈妈
He should have his pitching arm back in no time.
他扭伤的胳膊很快就会好
-thank you
-谢谢
but I want ask m.j. said that he fell on purpose
但我仍要问一下  m.j.说他故意摔的
Something about you telling him
是关于你们跟他说的
To "let daddy push the elevator button"?
让爸爸去按那个电梯的按钮
You told him to fall?
你让他故意摔倒
Remember, it's the pavement you're mad at.
记着  你该冲人行道发火
What the hell susan? why would you do something like that
怎么回事  苏珊  你为什么要那么做
Jackson taught him to ride the bike.
是杰克逊教他骑的车
Jackson.
杰克逊
Who's jackson?
谁是杰克逊
He does sleepovers with mommy.
他和妈妈过夜
They drink lots of wine.
他们喝了好多酒
Hey, doc. don't you hand out lollipops to brave little boys?
医生  你是不是该拿棒棒糖  去哄哄小孩
I'm sorry. m.j. was excited about the bike,
抱歉  m.j.看到自行车太兴奋了
So jackson took off the training wheels
所以杰克逊卸下了护轮
And taught him. he didn't know.
就教他了  他不知道
He didn't know I'd wanna be the one
他不知道我才是那个
-To teach my own kid how to ride a bike?
-该教我儿子骑车的人吧
you know what
我跟你讲
This is not jackson's fault.
这不是杰克逊的错
You can't give a 5-year-old a bike
你不该给一个5岁的孩子自行车
And expect him to wait to ride it until you have time.
然后期望他等你有时间再骑
You know, this is what it means to be divorced.
离婚就是这样
It means that sometimes you won't be there.
有时候你不能到场
I know.
我知道
Just harder
太难了
Than I thought it would be.
比我预料的更难
Well, it's hard for me, too.
对我来说也很难
I miss things when he's with you.
我怀念他和你在一起的时光
And i...
而且我
Am trying to come to terms with my guilt, because...
努力去面对我的过错  因为
I have to.
我必须这么做
So do you.
你也一样
There's nothing else you can do.
除此之外  你什么都做不了
Has mike called?
麦克打电话来了么
Hi, honey. you're home.
亲爱的  你回来啦
Sorry, hon.
对不起  亲爱的
So did he call?
他打过电话么
No.
没有
Hey, listen to this.
看看这个
Mrs. hudson's putting her house up for sale.
哈德孙太太出售她家的房子
I think we should buy it.
我想我们应该买下来
Why?
为什么
As an investment. i-i mean, it's fantastic.
作为一种投资  这很不错
My friend mary alice blew her brains out in this house,
我朋友玛丽·艾莉丝在这里饮弹自尽
And all I'd have to do is let that slip,
我可以无意地说出那个秘密
And we'd get it for a song.
那多好玩啊
yeah. I don't think so.
我不这么想
Well, why not? we'll rent it out.
为什么不  我们把它租出去
We could make some serious money.
我们可以正经地赚钱
last thing I wanna be is a landlord,
我可不想做房主
Get a phone call every time a toilet overflows.
每次厕所进水  电话吵个不停
That's why we hire a management company
所以我们才雇佣物业公司
damn it, edie, I said no!
该死  伊迪  我说了不行
Why are you yelling at me?
你冲我喊什么
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm sorry. I just got a lot on my mind.
抱歉  我最近太心烦了
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Hi, bethany.
贝瑟妮
I'm here to pick up juanita. is she around?
我来接胡安妮塔的  她在吗
Boys have sperm.
男孩子有精液
Excuse me?
你说什么
We need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
So apparently, after we had our little chat with juanita,
很显然  在我们和胡安妮塔谈过之后
She went straight to bethany
她直接去贝瑟妮家了
And passed on the facts of life in excruciating detail.
转述了生活上那些痛苦的细节
Well, did you explain to peggy why we had the little chat?
你向佩吉解释我们那个谈话了么
She didn't wanna hear it,
她不想听
Not with bethany running around the house,
而且还不止  贝瑟妮满屋子跑
Screaming "intercourse!" at the top of her lungs.
嘶声裂肺的大喊  "性交"
So we're out of the playdate?
-小孩的聚会没戏了
oh, yeah. way out.
是的  出局了
Well, I guess it's back to the old schedule
我觉得该执行老计划了
Of ten minutes of grope 'n snore at midnight.
在午夜打鼾的时候10分钟搞定
I'm not going back, carlos. I can't.
我不想回到以前  卡洛斯  我办不到
If juanita doesn't get her playdate,
如果胡安妮塔找不回她的玩伴
-You're not getting yours.
-你也别想有欢娱
fine. I will fix it.
好吧  我知道了
I just don't know why
我不知道为什么
Peggy's making such a big deal out of this.
佩吉要对此事大动干戈
Sperm!
精液
Juanita! stop talking to your sister!
胡安妮塔  不许跟你妹妹说
Orson, what are you doing in the guest bedroom?
奥森  你在客房干吗呢
Oh, I couldn't sleep.
我睡不着
You were snoring too loudly.
你打鼾声音太响了
Me? snoring?
我  打鼾
Mm, like a donkey with a head cold.
像一只伤风了的猴子
Honey, I don't snore.
亲爱的  我不打鼾的
Oh, you can't always hear yourself.
你自己也听不到
But I hear you...
但是我能听到
Loud and clear.
很大声  很清晰
Oh, for heaven sakes, come back to bed.
我的天  回去睡觉吧
No.
不
I'm good here.
我在这挺好
dave williams.
大卫.威廉姆斯
Look, hate to bother you,
很抱歉打扰你
But I got a busted pipe outside the house.
我房子外面的管道裂了
Probably some kids playing a prank.
-可能是小孩子搞得恶作剧
no problem.
没问题
I'm across town finishing up on another job.
我正在别的镇工作
So depending on traffic, give me... say an hour?
-看交通情况吧  给我一个小时
oh, thanks.
谢谢
I really appreciate it.
不胜感激
So when juanita thought that I might be hurting her mother,
当胡安妮塔觉得我是在伤害她妈妈时
We decided it was best that she knew the truth.
我们决定最好让她知道真相
It just seemed like the right thing to do at the time.
就像在那个时候刚好做了那事
See, honey?
看到没  亲爱的
I-i knew there had to be a rational explanation.
我就知道他们有合理解释的
I guess under the circumstances,
我猜在那种情况下
You didn't have any other choice.
你们没有别的选择
So... do you think there's any chance
那胡安妮塔有没有机会
Juanita could rejoin your playdate?
再加入聚会呢
we've talked to her.
我们已经跟她说了
She will never discuss sex ever again.
她以后再也不会讨论性了
Not if she wants to see her favorite dolly alive.
不然她最喜欢的娃娃肯定会遭殃
Gaby, we don't need to let them know
加布  我们不必让他们知道
All of our parenting secrets.
我们夫妻间的所有秘密
I... think that'd be okay.
我想没事了
I probably overreacted.
我可能是反应过激了
We just want keep bethany's innocence as long as we can
我们只想尽可能地维持贝瑟妮的天真
Oh, we totally agree.
我们完全同意
-Kids are grow up way too fast these days.
-孩子们最近成熟得太快了
no kidding.
没错
I want my girls to believe in santa as long as possible.
我尽可能让我女儿相信圣诞老人
They're gonna find out soon enough that it's all a lie.
她们很快会发现这是个十足的谎言
What?
什么
There's no santa claus?!
没有圣诞老人吗
Next playdate's monday at 1:00?
下次聚会是定在周一1:00吗
Wow, whoever did this really went to town.
谁干的  都能出名了
Yeah, I know. damn kids.
是啊  我也知道  该死的孩子
By the way,
顺便说一句
Did you put any more thought into joining the band?
有没有再考虑一下  加入乐队
Oh, man. I'm sorry. I've been meaning to get back to you.
抱歉  我很想加入
I appreciate the offer,
真的很感激你们找我
But I'm really stretched thin these days.
但最近真的忙坏了
Oh, come on. every man's got time for a little music.
好吧  谁都有听听小曲的时间的
Believe me, I'd love to play with you guys,
相信我  我很乐意跟你们一起玩玩
But, uh, I live 30 minutes away, an hour in traffic.
但是  我在路上就能耽误1小时
-Whatever time I've got left's for my son.
-留给我儿子的就没多长时间了
yeah, I hear ya
我理解
Hey, you ever look into living a little closer by?
你想过搬到近一点的地方住吗
With the rent prices in this neighborhood?
但附近的租金太贵了
I might play guitar like a rock star,
我吉他是弹得像个明星
-But I don't earn like one.
-但没有明星那么有钱
yeah. sorry.
对不起
-I wasn't thinking.
-我说话不经大脑
oh, it's all right.
没关系
Uh, appreciate you trying to help.
谢谢你  你有心了
Believe me, I wish I could do more.
相信我  我希望我能帮忙
I've never seen Bree so happy. she's glowing.
从没见过布里那么高兴  闪闪发光
She won't be glowing when that agency sinks her book.
等广告商糟蹋了她的书  她就不发光
Lynette...
勒奈特
I'm telling you, the only thing staler than that ad campaign
告诉你  那个广告宣传糟糕透顶
Is this dinner roll.
这面包圈和宣传一样糟
yeah, and the water was as flat as the ad campaign.
宣传做得和水一样平淡无奇
Your martini was as dry as the ad campaign. let it go.
和你的马蒂尼酒一样枯燥乏味  看开点
Hi, everybody! you having a good time?
-大家好  开心吗
hi!
你好
Hey, beautiful!
你好  美人
Um ,this is-- Stu!
这是斯图
Hey.
你好
Everyone, this is my old assistant,
大家  这是我以前的助理
-Stu, um...
-斯图  呃
Durber.
都伯
Hey! well, this was one great guy.
他人非常的好
He would schlep all the way across town
以前会跑遍整个镇
Just to get me my chinese food.
帮我买中国菜
So...What are you up to?
那么  你现在做什么
Actually, Stu's company is doing all my advertising.
事实上  斯图的公司负责我的宣传
Your company? you have a company?
你的公司  你开了家公司
Three years now. huh.
已经三年了
How about you? are you still at, uh, Parcher & Murphy?
你呢  你还在波特&摩非公司吗
No, i... also went into business for myself.
不  我  现在也是自己创业
Her place makes the best pizza in town.
她店里的披萨是镇上一流的
You own a pizzeria?
你开了披萨店
Well, it's really my husband's.
应该说是我丈夫开的
And I'm still doing some freelance stuff.
我算是自由职业者
Well, that's great. you know, we're always working late.
太棒了  我们总是要加班
Give me your card. we'll order from you some night. oh.
给我你的名片  我们可以向你们定披萨
You know, of course, we're across town,
你知道  我们在镇的另一边
So it may be a bit of a schlep. oh!
所以可能要跑跑腿
-It was great catching up, Lynette.
-很高兴能叙叙旧  勒奈特
yeah.
当然
Bree, let me introduce you to some people.
布里  我介绍你认识一些人
There's my beautiful wife.
我美丽的老婆在这里
What are you up to?
你在忙什么
Why? looking for a reason to scream at me?
为什么问我  想找理由吼我吗
You're right. I was awful the other day.
你说的对  我那天太过分了
How about I make it up to you
为了补偿你
By buying you Mrs. Hudson's house?
我买下哈德森太太的房子怎么样
Seriously?
-真的吗
well, I thought about it, and I agree.
我考虑过了  我觉得
It's a good investment opportunity.
这的确是个好的投资机会
Oh! thank you!
谢谢你
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. thank you. thank you.
谢谢你  谢谢你
And I promise that we'll rent that place out for top dollar.
我保证  我们会收到很高的租金
Oh, I'm not worried about that.
我倒不担心这个
But first... I want to do someone a favor.
但是我想帮别人一个忙
Hi.
你好
Where are you? it's after 2:00.
你在哪  都两点多了
I'm getting ready for my job interview.
我在准备面试
Oh, that's not until 4:00.
面试4点才开始
I'm reading the company's annual reports.
我在看公司的年度报告
I want to be prepared.
需要充分准备
Oh, honey. everybody's asking about you.
亲爱的  很多人都问起你
I want you to be here. it's my big day.
我想你在这  今天对我很重要
Well...Enjoy it.You've earned it.
好好享受  你应得的
You know what this tastes like? more.
知道这东西多好吃吗  再来点
It would seem
似乎
Somebody's taking their designated driver position...
有人对自己的旧部下爬到自己头上来
-A little lightly.
-过于在意
Stu?
斯图
Stu is doing Bree's ad campaign?
斯图负责布里的宣传
I rode in his hatchback once.
我坐过他的车
It smelled like mu shu.
车里味道烂透了
I gotta warn her.
-我必须警告她
oh, wait! no, honey.
等等  亲爱的
Why don't you wait till after the ceremony?
庆功宴结束再说吧
Yeah, just until you can blink both eyes at the same time.
是呀  等到你酒醒了以后
Guys, I am just gonna offer her a little advice. geesh.
朋友们  我只是给她提点意见
Whoop. still waiting.
还在等你上菜呢
The great thing about the internet is that
网络的最大优点就是
With a minimal investment, you actually can reach
用最小的投资  你能向固定的目标群体
-All your specific target audience
-做宣传
coupons.
优惠券
Coupons?
Do a cross-promotion
和一些大型食物公司
with some of the major food companies.Knock off 20%
合作促销  降低20%的售价
On some of the items featured in your recipes,
销售你书上的美食
Then they do the same
如果购买你的书
Towards the purchase of your cookbook.
也降低20%的售价
Yeah, our research shows, you know,
根据我们最近的调查报告
-People aren't so hot on gimmicks
-人们对这些噱头并不感兴趣
zip it, Stewie.
住嘴  斯图
Would you excuse us, please?
我们走开一下
Lynette, you're drunk.
勒奈特  你醉了
Yeah, that's immaterial.
那不重要
What do you think of the coupons?
你觉得优惠券怎么样
Lynette, I am really not able to deal with that right now.
勒奈特  我现在不想讨论这个
Oh. I know.
我知道
You've got your book and your big fancy award,
你出了书  还得了奖
And I'm just a housewife.
我只是个家庭主妇
I never said that.
我没这么想
You know, when I had a high-powered career, and you
当我叱咤风云
were just a housewife, I never looked down on you.
而你只是家庭主妇的时候  我没小看过你
If you could all please take your seats,
大家请就座
It's time to present our award.
颁奖时间到了
You need to leave now.
你现在得走了
Fine. and don't worry. Even though I'd like to
好  别担心  不管我多想
I'm not gonna make some big, ugly scene.
我都不会闹场的
Hi.
你好
Hey. I, um, I bought M.J. some stilts,
我给MJ买了自行车
Thought I'd teach him how to use 'em.
我现在准备教他骑
Har har. uh, actually, he's at Juanita's watching a dvd.
事实上  他和胡安妮塔在看DVD
Do you want me to call him?
-我去叫他吧
No. no, it's cool.
不  不用了
I just wanted to tell him about my new place.
我只是想告诉他我搬家了
You're moving again?
你又搬家了
How far are you gonna be away now?
这次搬多远
The Hudson house?
-哈德森的房子
yeah, she sold it.
是的  她卖掉了
And Edie told me the new owner wants to rent it,
伊迪说新房东要出租
So now I'll have a fighting chance
现在我有机会
Of being around when m.j. hits his milestones.
在MJ身边  看着他成长
Is this okay with you?
你没意见吧
Yeah. it's great.
这太棒了
Uh, we'll be like...One big, happy, divorced family.
我们就像一个离了婚大家庭
You sure?
你确定
It's a little weird.
有点奇怪
I--i but, you know, m.j. will be thrilled, and...
但是MJ会很开心
Yeah, I'm fine with it.
所以我也没问题
Good.
好
So, um...I'll see you around, neighbor.
那么  回头见  邻居
I still think it's strange
我还是觉得很奇怪
You won't let me tell Mike that we're the new owners.
为什么不告诉迈克  我们是新房东
Well, the man's got a lot of pride.
他是个自尊心很强的人
I want him to feel like I'm his neighbor, not his landlord.
我想让他把我当成邻居  而不是房东
Landlord? hell, with the rent we're charging him,
房东  见鬼  那么点房租
You're his fairy godmother.
你简直就是他的神仙教母
All right, consider it an investment in good karma.
你可以想想好人有好报
Screw karma.
见它的鬼去
I finally do something nice in this neighborhood,
我好不容易做了件好事
N't even brag about it?
却不能告诉别人
The man who is silent in his good deeds
做了好事而不张扬的人
Is the man who reaps the greatest reward.
才是最大的赢家
-Hey.
-你好
Hi.
你好
So...Give me some guidance.
给我点提示
Do I grovel, send flowers, or...Just move?
我要不要跪下  送花  还是该搬家
I'm not angry with you.
我没有生你的气
I'm just sorry that you felt so--
我只是很抱歉让你
Drunk? jealous?
喝醉  妒忌
You have nothing to be jealous of.
我没什么值得你妒忌的
Don't give me that.
别这么说
You are having the kind of success
你目前的成功
I only dreamed of back in my ad days.
是我做广告的时候梦寐以求的
But that doesn't mean I look down on you.
但这不代表我小看你
No. but watching you, I look down on me.
不  但你的成功  让我自形惭愧
When I held your book in my hands,
当我拿着你的书
I felt so jealous my stomach hurt.
我妒忌到胃绞痛
And I thought, if I could just hitch a ride,
然后我就想  如果我能搭下顺风车
Have a piece of it,
分享一下成功
I wouldn't feel so bad about your success.
也许我就不会那么妒忌
For god sakes, Lynette, stop calling me a success.
看在上帝的份上  勒奈特  别再说我成功
There's nothing successful about me.
我根本就一事无成
My friends think I'm gonna drop them,
我的朋友觉得我不会丢下他们